module.exports = {
  gameType: 'text',
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'What does the word dinosaur mean?',
      a: 'Nasty Creature',
      b: 'Ancient Fossil',
      c: 'Giant Beast',
      d: 'Terrible Lizard',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'What was the first dinosaur to be discovered?',
      a: 'Baryonyx',
      b: 'Megalosaurus',
      c: 'Diplodocus',
      d: 'Stegosaurus',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'What is one predominant question scientists have not entirely agreed upon about dinosaurs?',
      a: 'Did dinosaurs lay eggs?',
      b: 'What exactly caused their extinction?',
      c: 'Were dinos warm or cold blooded?',
      d: 'What did they evolve from?',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'Scientists primarily believe the T-Rex had arms primarily for…',
      a: 'Nothing - they’re vestigial',
      b: 'Slashing their prey',
      c: 'Grabbing their kin',
      d: 'Hugs!!',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'On which continent have most dinosaur fossils been found?',
      a: 'Antarctica',
      b: 'North America',
      c: 'Africa',
      d: 'Asia',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'The best preserved T. rex skeleton (90%+!!) lives at The Field Museum in Chicago. What’s her name?',
      a: 'Maggie',
      b: 'Betty',
      c: 'Sue',
      d: 'Elizabeth',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'Dinosauria contains two major classifications of dinosaurs. What is the distinguisher between them?',
      a: 'Teeth Shape',
      b: 'Leg Build',
      c: 'Brain Size',
      d: 'Hip Structure',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'A T.Rex is a therapod. What does Therapod Mean?',
      a: 'Hollow-Boned',
      b: 'Beast-Footed',
      c: 'Carnivorous-Creature',
      d: 'Quick-Runner',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'Jurassic Park is a bit of a misleading name. What era were most of the park’s dinos from?',
      a: 'Cretaceous',
      b: 'Triassic',
      c: 'Silurian',
      d: 'Ordovician',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which dinosaur are you desperately searching for on the Animal Kingdom Ride, Dinosaur? ',
      a: 'Carnotaurus',
      b: 'Saltasaurus',
      c: 'Parasaurolophus',
      d: 'Iguanadon',
      answer: 'd'
    }
  ]
};
 